Previously on the show.
Episode sebelumnya.
The cannon Wolffy accidentally fired hit the weather tree,
Meriam Wolffy tak sengaja menembak pohon cuaca,
making it unable to produce weather fruits.
membuatnya tak bisa menghasilkan buah cuaca.
When the last weather seed was finally found,
Saat benih cuaca terakhir ditemukan,
Paddi swallowed it.
Paddi menelannya.
What will he and the others do next?
Apa yang akan dia dan lainnya lakukan selanjutnya?
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: Running Paddi."
Petualangan Langit Pulau Terbang: Paddi Berlari.
What? Paddi ate the last weather seed?
Apa?
Look at his head. It has sprouted.
Lihat kepalanya. Benihnya sudah tumbuh.
There's never been a case of a weather seed growing on a person.
Tak pernah ada kasus benih cuaca tumbuh pada diri seseorang.
Paddi, do you feel anything different?
Apa kau merasakan sesuatu yang berbeda?
I feel dizzy.
Aku merasa pusing.
Could it be a side effect from the weather seed?
Mungkin itu efek samping dari benih cuaca?
No. Based on my years of experience,
Tidak. Dari pengalamanku selama bertahun-tahun,
Paddi is probably just dizzy from hunger.
Paddi pusing hanya karena kelaparan.
Weslie knows me best.
Weslie sangat mengenalku.
Look. He's feeling energized now.
Lihat. Kini dia merasa berenergi.
A bit of pepper will be perfect.
Sedikit merica akan sempurna.
Is it finished already?
Apa sudah habis?
Paddi, what's that on your head?
Paddi, apa itu di kepalamu?
A wind fruit grew on your head!
Buah angin tumbuh di kepalamu!
No way.
Tak mungkin.
Who knew Paddi's sneeze would yield a wind fruit?
Siapa yang duga Paddi akan menghasilkan buah angin?
Could we get other fruits if Paddi did something else?
Apa bisa dapat buah lain jika Paddi melakukan hal lain?
Let's give it a try.
Mari kita coba.
I see. Sweating gives us rain fruit.
Begitu. Berkeringat menghasilkan buah hujan.
What if he sweated more?
Bagaimana kalau dia lebih berkeringat?
Paddi, keep running. Don't stop.
Paddi, terus lari. Jangan berhenti.
It worked. The more he sweats, the bigger the fruit is.
Bisa! Makin berkeringat, makin besar buahnya.
Let me make you a gigantic rain fruit.
Biar kubuat buah hujan raksasa.
Sorry.
Maaf.
Snoring gives us thunder fruits.
Mendengkur memberi buah petir.
We're running low on weather fruits.
Kami mulai kehabisan buah cuaca.
If we don't get more soon, we'll be in big trouble.
Jika tak ada pasokan baru, kita akan dalam masalah besar.
Yes, more and more orders are on hold.
Ya, makin banyak pesanan ditangguhkan.
Don't worry, everyone.
Tenang, Semuanya.
We have a temporary way of producing weather fruits.
Ada cara sementara untuk menghasilkan buah cuaca.
Leave it to me.
Serahkan kepadaku.
Do your best, Paddi. I'll be with you the whole time.
Berusahalah, Paddi Akan selalu kutemani.
All right, let's begin.
Baik, mari kita mulai.
Keep it up, Paddi. Keep going!
Semangat, Paddi! Semangat!
This is strange. Where did Weslie go?
Ini aneh. Weslie ke mana?
Why is there a telescope here?
Kenapa ada binokular di sini?
Hope, have you seen Weslie?
Hope, kau lihat Weslie?
I haven't, not today.
Belum lihat hari ini.
What was that sound?
Suara apa itu?
What's going on?
Ada apa?
I haven't seen you all day. Have you been sleeping?
Aku tak melihatmu seharian. Apa kau terus tidur?
Didn't you say you'd be with me?
Katanya kau akan menemaniku?
I'm doing all the hard work here.
Aku sedang bekerja keras.
I'm starving.
Aku lapar. Aku beli makanan dahulu.
Weslie, get up. It's time for dinner.
Weslie, bangun. Saatnya makan malam.
Let me take your mark energy,
Biar kuambil energi tandanya,
and turn you into a goat feast.
lalu siapkan kau untuk jamuan kambing.
Where's my energy extractor? Where is it?
Mana pengekstrak energiku? Di mana?
Weslie! Weslie, wake up!
Weslie!
So you're awake.
Rupanya kau sudah bangun.
I... I'm not. Look, I'm asleep.
Belum. Lihat, aku masih tidur.
I wouldn't have caught Weslie so easily if it was not for you.
Berkat kau, aku bisa mudah menangkap Weslie.
Thank you so much, Paddi.
Terima kasih banyak, Paddi.
What?
Apa?
Weslie exhausted himself trying to help you.
Weslie menghabiskan waktu berusaha membantumu.
Help me?
Membantuku?
I know you've been busy making weather fruits these days.
Aku tahu kau sedang sibuk membuat buah cuaca.
I must catch you all this time.
Aku harus segera menangkapmu.
Where is Weslie?
Di mana Weslie?
Wolffy!
Wolffy!
Bye.
Sampai jumpa.
Why is there a telescope here?
Kenapa ada binokular di sini?
Here's my chance.
Ini kesempatanku.
You again?
Kau lagi?
What was that sound?
Suara apa itu?
Wolffy!
Wolffy!
Great, two birds with one stone.
Sambil menyelam, minum air.
After being tricked so many times, I came prepared this time.
Setelah diperdaya berkali-kali, kali ini aku sudah siap.
Are you prepared for this then?
Kau sudah siap untuk ini?
What's going on?
Ada apa?
Because of my persistence, Weslie is finally exhausted.
Karena kegigihanku, Weslie akhirnya kelelahan.
Without Weslie's protection, catching both of you is a piece of cake.
Tanpa perlindungan Weslie, mudah menangkap kalian berdua.
I've... I've misunderstood Weslie.
Aku...
Do you think it's easy to catch you? Whatever.
Kau pikir mudah untuk menangkapmu? Terserah.
Extracting your energy is more important.
Mengekstrak energimu lebih penting.
Let go of Weslie!
Lepaskan Weslie!
Be patient. You're next.
Bersabarlah. Kau berikutnya.
What should I do? Oh, right!
Aku harus bagaimana?
That's weird. What is the problem?
Ini aneh. Apa masalahnya?
Do you think you can get away?
Kau mau kabur?
How dare you actually try to run away?
Beraninya kau mencoba kabur?
Stop!
Berhenti!
Paddi has gotten more capable lately.
Paddi jadi lebih hebat belakangan ini.
How can he run so long without getting tired?
Bagaimana dia bisa berlari tanpa lelah?
These weather fruits don't work on me anymore.
Buah cuaca ini tak bisa mengerjaiku lagi.
Why is it raining so hard?
Kenapa hujannya amat deras?
Don't underestimate the rainstorm fruit, Wolffy.
Jangan meremehkan buah badai hujan, Wolffy.
I won't let you get away, Paddi!
Tak akan kubiarkan kau lolos!
You're done.
Tamat riwayatmu.
No way.
Tak mungkin.
I will be back!
Aku akan kembali!
Paddi?
Paddi?
You're finally awake, Weslie.
Kau akhirnya sadar, Weslie.
Why are we here?
Kenapa kita di sini?
We were captured by Wolffy,
Kita ditangkap oleh Wolffy,
but it's all fine now.
tapi kini semua sudah aman.
No matter what happens, I'll protect you from now on.
Apa pun yang terjadi, mulai sekarang aku akan melindungimu.
Thank you, Paddi.
Terima kasih, Paddi.
Why didn't you tell me about all Wolffy's ambushes?
Kenapa kau tak cerita soal penyergapan Wolffy?
Weslie, I was afraid you'd be scared stiff.
Weslie, aku takut kau akan jadi takut.
What? I'm going home.
Apa?
Just kidding. Wait for me.
Hanya bercanda. Tunggu aku.
TO BE CONTINUED 2776 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
BERSAMBUNG 2.776 HARI SEBELUM PULANG